Guide to the Stanford University Newspaper Clippings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University newspaper clippings
1931-1990
SC0657
Peninsula Times Tribune..
Peninsula Times Tribune.
12.5 Linear feet
These clippings pertaining to Stanford University, the Stanford University Medical Center, Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, and Hoover Institution were selected from the morgue of the Peninsula Times Tribune after its closing. The clippings are arranged by subject and person.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Peninsula Times Tribune was organized in April 1979 from a merger of the Palo Alto Times and the Redwood City Tribune, both owned by the parent company Peninsula Newspapers Incorporated. The paper ceased publishing in 1993.
Description of the Collection
These clippings pertaining to Stanford University, the Stanford University Medical Center, Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, and Hoover Institution were selected from the morgue of the Peninsula Times Tribune after its closing. The clippings are arranged by subject and person.
Access Terms
Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace; Peninsula Times Tribune.; Stanford Linear Accelerator Center; Stanford University -- General subdivision--Sports.;; Stanford University. Department of Athletics.; Stanford University. Medical Center.
Collection Contents
- Clippings, Accession ARCH-1995-075
  - Athletes in Action (Box 1)
  - Cake Wizardry (Box 1)
  - California Air and Space Center (Box 1)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (I) (Box 1)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (II) (Box 1)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (III) (Box 1)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (IV) (Box 1)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (V) (Box 1)
  - Children's Hospital at Stanford (VII) (Box 1)
  - College Bowl (Box 1)
  - College of American Pathologists (Box 1)
  - Color-Blind (Box 1)
  - "Compact City" (Box 1)
  - Computer Museum (Box 1)
  - Cryptography (Box 1)
  - Cyclotron (Box 1)
  - DNA (deoxyribonucleic acid) (III) (Box 1)
  - DNA (V) (Box 1)
  - Ensemble Chanterelle (Box 1)
  - Escondido Village (Box 1)
  - Fallen Leaf Camp Association (Box 1)
  - First Church of Nazarene (Box 1)
  - Hughes Medical Research Institute (Box 1)
  - Holiday House at Stanford (Box 1)
  - Hoover Commission (Box 1)
  - Hoover, Herbert Government Reorganization 1949 (I) (Box 1)
  - Hoover, Herbert Government Reorganization 1949 (II) (Box 1)
  - Hoover, Herbert Government Reorganization - Comments, Reports, Talks (Box 1)
  - Hoover Government Reorganization - Citizens' Committee and Other Groups (I) (Box 1)
  - Hoover Government Reorganization - Citizens' Committee and Other Groups (II) (Box 1)
  - Hoover House (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution through 1959 (I) (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1960-1965 (II) (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1966-1969 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1970-1979 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1980 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1983 Jan.-June (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1983 Jul.-Dec. (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1984 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1985 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1988 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1989 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1990 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1991 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution 1992 (Box 1)
  - Hoover Institution booklet (Box 1)
  - Hoover Library - Collections, Contents 1932-1945 (I) (Box 1)
  - Hoover Library - Collections, Contents 1946-1956 (II) (Box 1)
  - Hoover Library - Collections, Contents 1957- (III) (Box 1)
  - Hoover Presidential Library (Herbert Hoover) (Box 1)
  - Hoover Tower (Box 1)
  - Hubbard Street Dance Company (Box 1)
  - Hurler's Disease ("gargoylism") (Box 1)
  - Inside Stanford (Box 1)
  - Institute for the Advancement of Human Behavior (Box 1)
  - Lake Lagunita (I) (Box 1)
  - Lake Lagunita (II) (Box 1)
  - Pine Hills (Box 1)
  - Polo/ Ralph Lauren Corp. (Box 1)
  - Powerhouse (Box 1)
  - Reagan Library 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Reagan Library 1987 (Box 1)
  - Reagan Library 1988- (Box 1)
  - Reformed Druids of North America (Box 1)
  - Research Libraries Group (Box 1)
  - Research Libraries Group (Box 1)
  - Rodin Sculpture Garden - Stanford University SEE: Stanford University Cantor Garden (Box 1)
  - "Round Three" (housing development) (Box 1)
  - Sleep Disorders Clinic through 1979 (Box 1)
  - Sleep Disorders Clinic 1980-1984 (Box 1)
  - Sleep Disorders Clinic 1985-1989 (Box 1)
  - Sleep Disorders Clinic 1990- (Box 1)
  - Stanford Antiquarian Book Fair (Box 1)
  - Stanford Area Chinese Club (Box 1)
  - Stanford Associates (Box 1)
  - Stanford Bank, Palo Alto (Box 1)
  - Stanford Barn (Box 1)
  - Stanford Barn Box Office (Box 1)
  - Stanford Business Conference (Box 1)
  - Stanford Crew (also Stanford Crew Fund) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Diving Club (Box 1)
  - Stanford Environmental Law Society (Box 1)
  - Stanford Historical Society (Box 1)
  - Stanford Independent (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center 1977-79 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center 1980-81 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center 1982-83 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center 1984-86 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center 1987-89 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center 1990- (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - Linear Collider (Box 1)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center - TLC (Box 1)
  - Stanford Medical Group (Box 1)
  - Stanford Music Hall (Box 1)
  - Stanford Opera Workshop (Box 1)
  - Stanford Organized for Academic Responsibility (Box 1)
  - Stanford/ Palo Alto Homecoming Parade and Street Party (Box 1)
  - Stanford Players (Box 1)
  - Stanford Progressive Alliance (Box 1)
  - Stanford Public Interest Law Foundation (Box 1)
  - Stanford Savoyards (for previous clippings, see Stanford Univ. Music and Stanford Univ. Theater) (Box 1)
  - Stanford Vision Clinic (Box 1)
  - Stanford Wine Company (Box 1)
  - Stanford Women in Science and Engineering (Box 1)
  - Stanford Workshop on Political and Social Issues (SWOPSI) (Box 1)
  - SOAR (SEE: Stanford Organized for Academic Responsibility) (Box 1)
  - United Stanford Employees through 1979 (Box 1)
  - United Stanford Workers 1980-82 (Box 1)
  - United Stanford Workers 1983-85 (Box 1)
  - United Stanford Workers 1986- (Box 1)
  - Young Men's Christian Association - Fitness Center, Stanford Industrial park (Box 1)
  - Webb Ranch through 1989 (Box 1)
  - Palo Alto Times (no envelope) (Box 1)
  - Stanford University
    - General (Box 2)
    - General 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder o2)
    - General 1980 (Box 2, Folder o3)
    - General 1981 (Box 2, Folder o4)
    - General 1982 (Box 2)
    - General 1983 Jan.-June (Box 2)
    - General 1983 Jul.-Dec. (Box 2)
    - General 1984 Jan.-June (Box 2)
    - General 1984 Jul.-Dec. (Box 2)
    - General 1985 (Box 2)
    - General 1986-87 (Box 2)
    - General 1988-89 (Box 2)
    - General 1990- (Box 2)
    - Academic Council (Box 2)
    - Academic Senate (Box 2)
    - Administration (Box 2)
    - Administration (Box 2)
    - Admissions/ Enrollment (I) (Box 2)
    - Admissions/ Enrollment (II) (Box 2)
    - Advisory Board (Box 2)
    - Alcohol and Drug Treatment Center 1991 (previous file lost) (Box 2)
    - Alfred R. Masters Memorial Grove (Box 2)
    - Alumni through 1979 (Box 2)
    - Alumni 1980- (Box 2)
    - Alumni and Foreign Policy (Box 2)
    - Alumni House (Bowman) (Box 2)
    - Amateur Radio Club W6YX (Box 2)
    - Animal Research Center (Box 2)
    - Animal Research Facility (Box 2)
    - Annexations (Box 2)
    - Annexation (Box 2)
    - Anniversaries (see also Stanford Univ. history) (Box 2)
    - Anthropology Department (Box 2)
    - Anti-Draft Union (Box 2)
    - Applied Electronics Laboratory (Box 2)
    - Arboretum (Box 2)
    - Architecture Dept. (Box 2)
    - Archives Dept. (Box 2)
    - Arena (Box 2)
    - Art (SEE: S.U. museums) (Box 2)
    - Art Dept. (Box 2)
    - Art Dept. and artists in residence and art fellowships, scholarships, etc. (See also: Stanford Lectures - Art) (Box 2)
    - Art Exhibits - Tresidder, etc. (see also: Stanford Art Gallery, and Stanford Museum of Art) (Box 2)
    - Art Gallery (see also: Stanford Museum of Art, and Stanford Art Exhibits) (Box 2)
    - Art Studios (Box 2)
    - Artificial Intelligence Project (Box 2)
    - Asbestos Fibers (Box 2)
    - ASCEND Project (Advanced System for Communications and Education in Nat'l Development) (Box 2)
    - Asia Medical Fund (SAMFUND) (Box 2)
    - Asian-American (Box 2)
    - Associated Students (Box 2)
    - Associated Students Council of Presidents (Box 2)
    - Associated Student Travel Service (Box 2)
    - ASSU (see also: Stanford Univ. Student Legislature) (Box 2)
    - Associated Women Students (Box 2)
    - Associates (see also: Stanford Univ. Alumni Assn.) (Box 2)
    - Athletics (Box 2)
    - Atom Smasher and Research (see also: Stanford Linear Accelerator) (Box 2)
    - Aurora (Box 2)
    - Autonomy Movement (see also: Stanford Student Legislature) (Box 2)
    - Awards (Box 2)
    - Axe through 1949 (Box 2)
    - Axe 1950-59 (Box 2)
    - Axe 1960 (see also: S.U. Big Game) (Box 2)
    - Bail Fund (Box 2)
    - Balloons (Box 2)
    - Band (see also: Stanford Univ. Music - Band) (Box 2)
    - Band 1980-84 (Box 2)
    - Band 1985-89 (Box 2)
    - Band 1990- (Box 2)
    - Band Day (Box 2)
    - Beards (Box 2)
    - Bechtel International Center (Box 2)
    - Bequests (Box 2)
    - Bicycle Pathways, Bicycle Licensing (Box 2)
    - Big Game through 1959 (Box 2)
    - Big Game 1960-69 (Box 2)
    - Big Game 1970-79 (Box 2)
    - Big Game 1980-84 (Box 2)
    - Big Game 1985-89 (See also: SU Axe) (Box 2)
    - Big Game 1990- (see also: SU Axe) (Box 2)
    - Bing Nursery School and Day Camp (Box 2)
    - Biology Dept. (Box 2)
    - Birth Control Bills (Box 2)
    - Birthday Cake Agency (Box 2)
    - "Black Power" (Box 2)
    - Black Student Union (Box 2)
    - Black Student Volunteer Center (Box 2)
    - Blood Bank (Box 2)
    - Blue Garden (Box 2)
    - Board of Trustees through 1969 (Box 2)
    - Board of Trustees 1970-79 (Box 2)
    - Board of Trustees 1980-83 (Box 2)
    - Board of Trustees 1984-85 (Box 2)
    - Board of Trustees 1986-89 (Box 2)
    - Board of Trustees 1990- (Box 2)
    - Bomb Scares and Bombings (see also under: Bomb Scares, Local) (Box 2)
    - Books Projects (SEE: Stanford Overseas Books Projects) (Box 2)
    - Bookstore (Box 2)
    - Bookstore (Box 2)
    - Boys Town Center (Box 2)
    - Braun Music Center (see also: SU music) (Box 2)
    - Bridge, The (Box 2)
    - Buck Club (Box 2)
    - Budget through 1985 (Box 2)
    - Budget 1986- (Box 2)
    - Buildings through 1959 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1960-69 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1970-79 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1980-82 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1983-84 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1985-86 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1987 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1988 (Box 2)
    - Buildings 1989 (Box 2)
    - Burn Research (Box 2)
    - Bursar (Box 2)
    - Business Affairs Office (Box 2)
    - Business Conference (1948, 1956, 1957, 1960, 1962) (Box 2)
    - Business Conference (1962-63, 1964, 1966, 1967) (Box 2)
    - Business Development Assoc. (Box 2)
    - Business Library - J. Hugh Jackson Library. (Box 2)
    - Business School (Graduate) through 1969 (Box 2)
    - Business School (Graduate) 1970-79 (Box 2)
    - Business School (Graduate) 1980-84 (Box 2)
    - Business School (Graduate) 1985-89 (Box 2)
    - Business School (Graduate) 1990- (Box 2)
    - Business School Faculty, Staff, and Alumni (Box 2)
    - Cambodia (Box 2)
    - Campus 1970-80 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1981 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1982 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1983 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1984 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1985 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1986 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1987 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1988 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1989 (Box 2)
    - Campus 1990- (Box 2)
    - Campus Drive (Box 2)
    - Campus Judicial Panel (Box 2)
    - Campus Town (proposed) (Box 2)
    - Cannon (football) (Box 2)
    - Cantor Sculpture Garden (Box 2)
    - Cap and Gown (Box 2)
    - Cardinal Club (Box 2)
    - Cardinal Cogen (cogeneration plant) (Box 2)
    - Cardiovascular Research Center (Box 2)
    - Career Planning and Placement Center (Box 2)
    - Centennial through 1985 (Box 2)
    - Centennial 1986-1990 (Box 3)
    - Centennial 1991 (Box 3)
    - Centennial - Special Edition (Box 3)
    - Center for ... (Box 3)
    - Center for Advanced Studies in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 3)
    - Center for Communications Disorders (Box 3)
    - Center for Computer Research in Music and Acoustics (Box 3)
    - Center for East Asian Studies (Box 3)
    - Center for Economic Analysis of Human Behavior and Social Institutions (Box 3)
    - Center for Health Care Research (Box 3)
    - Center for Information Processing (Box 3)
    - Center for Innovation and Research in Education (Box 3)
    - Center for Integrated Electronics in Medicine (Box 3)
    - Center fort Integrated Systems (Box 3)
    - Center for Interdisciplinary Research (Box 3)
    - Center for Material Research (Box 3)
    - Center for Molecular and Genetic Research (Box 3)
    - Center for International Security and Arms Control (Box 3)
    - Center for Public Service (Box 3)
    - Center for Research and Development in Teaching (Box 3)
    - Center for Research in International Studies (Box 3)
    - Center for Space Science and Astrophysics (Box 3)
    - Center for Study of Families, Children and Youth (Box 3)
    - Central Intelligence Agency Contracts, etc. (Box 3)
    - Centrex telephone (Box 3)
    - Chaparral magazine (Box 3)
    - Chaparral (Box 3)
    - Charter (Box 3)
    - Chemistry Department and Chemistry Research (Box 3)
    - Chicano Program and Chicano Seminar Program (Box 3)
    - Child Care Center (proposed) (Box 3)
    - Child Care Centers (Box 3)
    - China Tour (Box 3)
    - "Choices" (Box 3)
    - Cigarette smoking (Box 3)
    - Circuits Laboratory (Box 3)
    - Citizens Advocates at Stanford, Inc. (Box 3)
    - City Services Zone (Palo Alto) (Box 3)
    - Classes (Box 3)
    - Clean Car Club (Box 3)
    - Clean-up and Paint-up (Box 3)
    - Clinic (Box 3)
    - Clock and Tower (Box 3)
    - Club Big Way (Box 3)
    - Coalition against the War in Indochina (Box 3)
    - Coalition for an Academic Community (Box 3)
    - Coeds (Box 3)
    - Coffee House (Box 3)
    - College Bowl (Box 3)
    - Colors (Box 3)
    - Columbae House (Box 3)
    - Commissary (Box 3)
    - Commission on Investment Responsibilities (Box 3)
    - Committee on Black Performing Arts (Box 3)
    - Committee on Minority Issues (Box 3)
    - Committee on Personal Safety (Box 3)
    - Committee on Public Events (Box 3)
    - Committee on Public Exercises (Box 3)
    - Committee on Research (Box 3)
    - Committee on Services to Stanford (Box 3)
    - Committee on Student Services (Box 3)
    - Committee to Retire Aspiring Politicos (Box 3)
    - Communications (Box 3)
    - Communications Department (Box 3)
    - Community against War and Fascism (Box 3)
    - Community College (Box 3)
    - Community Committee for International Students (Box 3)
    - Community Development Lab (Box 3)
    - Community Forum (Box 3)
    - Community Service Award (Box 3)
    - Computation Center (Box 3)
    - Computer-Assisted Instruction (Box 3)
    - Computer Science Department (Box 3)
    - Conference I (Box 3)
    - Conference II (Box 3)
    - Conference III (Box 3)
    - Conference on Education (Box 3)
    - Conference on Publishing (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1983 (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1984 (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1985 (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1986 (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1987 (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1988 (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - Conferences 1991 (Box 3)
    - "Conscience" (Box 3)
    - Convalescent Home (Box 3)
    - Convalescent Home Auxiliaries (Box 3)
    - Convalescent Home History (Box 3)
    - Corner Stone (Box 3)
    - Costume Collection (Box 3)
    - Council of Presidents (Box 3)
    - Council on Childcare (Box 3)
    - Counseling Services (Box 3)
    - Court Hearings (Box 3)
    - Cowell Health Center (Box 3)
    - Creative Writing Center (Box 3)
    - Crime (Box 3)
    - Crothers Hall (Box 3)
    - Cubberley Conference (Box 3)
    - Cummings Art Building (Box 3)
    - Curriculum I (Box 3)
    - Curriculum II (Box 3)
    - Curriculum 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Curriculum 1987 (Box 3)
    - Curriculum 1988 (Box 3)
    - Curriculum 1989 (Box 3)
    - Daily -1969 (Box 3)
    - Daily 1970-1977 (Box 3)
    - Daily 1978-1979 (Box 3)
    - Daily 1980- (Box 3)
    - Dames, the (Box 3)
    - Day of Concern (Box 3)
    - Daytime Stress and Sleep Project (Box 3)
    - Dean of Undergraduate Studies (Box 3)
    - Delta Gammas (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations -1969 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1970 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1974-1979 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1980-1983 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1984 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1985 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1986 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1989 (Box 3)
    - Demonstrations 1990 (Box 3)
    - Demonstration School (Box 3)
    - Dental Center (Box 3)
    - Department of Defense (Box 3)
    - Dinkelspeil Memorial Auditorium (Box 3)
    - Disabled Students (Box 3)
    - Disabled Student Services Office (Box 3)
    - Discipline (Box 3)
    - DNA Research (Box 3)
    - Dogs (Box 3)
    - Donald C. Power Laboratory (Box 3)
    - Donations (Box 3)
    - Dormitories (Box 3)
    - Draft (Box 3)
    - Draft (Box 3)
    - Drama Conference (Box 3)
    - Drama Department (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Festival of the Arts (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Independent Theater Groups (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Little Theater (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Master of Fine Arts (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Museum Series (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Productions (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Ram's Head (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Repertory Theater (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Repertory Theater (Box 3)
    - Drama -- Stanford Players (Box 3)
    - Drug/alcohol policy (Box 3)
    - Earth Sciences School (Box 3)
    - Earthquake Research (Box 3)
    - Eating Contest (Box 3)
    - Ecology College (Box 3)
    - Educated Woman Symposium (Box 3)
    - Education (Box 3)
    - Education (Box 3)
    - Education Conference 1958-1963 (Box 3)
    - Election Recess (Box 3)
    - Electrical Engineers (Box 3)
    - Electronic Research Laboratories (Box 3)
    - Electronics Machine Shop (Box 3)
    - El Toro Eating Club (Box 3)
    - Emeriti Undergraduate Council (Box 3)
    - Employees -1979 (Box 3)
    - Employees 1980-1981 (Box 3)
    - Employees 1982 (Box 3)
    - Employees 1983-1986 (Box 3)
    - Employees 1987-1989 (Box 3)
    - Employees 1990 (Box 3)
    - Employees Association (Box 3)
    - Encina Hall (Box 3)
    - Energy Conservation Center (Box 3)
    - Energy Management and Control System (Box 3)
    - Engineering Department (Box 3)
    - Engineers (Box 3)
    - English Department (Box 3)
    - Enrollment (Box 3)
    - Entrance (Box 3)
    - Environmental Law Society (Box 3)
    - Environmental Safety Facility (Box 3)
    - Espresso Bar (Box 3)
    - Experiment, The (Box 3)
    - Eye Bank (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1970-1974 (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1975-1978 (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1979 (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1980 (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1981 (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1982 (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1983 (Box 3)
    - Faculty 1984 (Box 4)
    - Faculty 1985 (Box 4)
    - Faculty 1986 (Box 4)
    - Faculty 1987 (Box 4)
    - Faculty 1988 (Box 4)
    - Faculty 1989 (Box 4)
    - Faculty -- Activities (Box 4)
    - Faculty Appointments and Awards (Box 4)
    - Faculty Appointments and Awards (Box 4)
    - Faculty Club (Box 4)
    - Faculty Emeriti (Box 4)
    - Faculty Political Action Committee (Box 4)
    - Faculty Wives (Box 4)
    - Fairs, Festivals (Box 4)
    - Falk Cardiovascular Research Center (Box 4)
    - Fellows (Box 4)
    - Fellowships (Box 4)
    - Fellowships, professorships (Box 4)
    - Feminist Union (Box 4)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary (Box 4)
    - Film Society (Box 4)
    - Finance -1979 (Box 4)
    - Finance 1980-1985 (Box 4)
    - Finance 1986-1991 (Box 4)
    - Finance 1992 (Box 4)
    - Fire Department (Box 4)
    - Fire Insurance (Box 4)
    - Fires 1931- (Box 4)
    - Flags (Box 4)
    - Food Research Institute (Box 4)
    - Food Services (Box 4)
    - Foothills Development (Box 4)
    - Foreign Language (Box 4)
    - Foreign Policy Institute (Box 4)
    - Foreign Students (Box 4)
    - Foreign Students (Box 4)
    - 4/10 Plan (Box 4)
    - Founders Day (Box 4)
    - Fraternities (Box 4)
    - Fraternities and Sororities 1984-1986 (Box 4)
    - Fraternities and Sororities 1987 (Box 4)
    - Free Campus Movement (Box 4)
    - French Film Series (Box 4)
    - Germany, Campus in (Box 4)
    - Gifts (Box 4)
    - Freshman Seminars (Box 4)
    - Frost Memorial Amphitheater (Box 4)
    - Fund (Box 4)
    - Garbage (Box 4)
    - Garbage (Box 4)
    - Gates Information Science Building (Box 4)
    - Gay People's Union (Box 4)
    - Genetics Department (Box 4)
    - Golf Course (Box 4)
    - Golf Course (Box 4)
    - Government Classified Studies (Box 4)
    - Gowns (Box 4)
    - Grading (Box 4)
    - Graduate Coordinating Committee (Box 4)
    - Graduate Education (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1945-1953 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1955 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1957 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1958 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1959-1962 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1964 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1965 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1966-1970 (Box 4)
    - Graduation (Box 4)
    - Graduation -1979 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1980-1984 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1985-1989 (Box 4)
    - Graduation 1990 (Box 4)
    - Grants I (Box 4)
    - Grants II (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Alpha Delta Phi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Alpha Kappa Lambda (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Alpha Sigma Phi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Alpha Tau Omega (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Alpha Tau Omicron (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Beta Chi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Beta Theta Pi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Chi Psi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Delta Chi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Delta Kappa Epsilon (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Delta Tau Delta (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Delta Tau Theta (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Delta Upsilon (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Kappa Alpha (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Kappa Alpha Theta (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Kappa Kappa Gamma (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Kappa Sigma (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Phi Alpha Delta (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Phi Beta Kappa (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Phi Delta Theta (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Phi Gamma Delta (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Phi Kappa Psi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Phi Kappa Sigma (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Pi Lambda Theta (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Sigma Alpha Epsilon (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Sigma Chi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Sigma Phi Epsilon (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Theta Chi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Theta Delta Chi (Box 4)
    - Greek Letter Organization -- Zeta Psi (Box 4)
    - Guide and Visitor Services (Box 4)
    - Hansen High Energy Lab (Box 4)
    - Haus Mitteleuropa (Box 4)